{
    "subject": "resource/Joan_Maragall",
    "predicate": "ontology/influencedBy",
    "object": "resource/Novalis",
    "human_readable": "Joan Maragall was influenced by Novalis.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9815406799316406,
            "question": "In what way did Novalis influence Joan Maragall?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8744562268257141,
            "question": "Who influenced Joan Maragall?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8689301013946533,
            "question": "What connection exists between Joan Maragall and Novalis?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.846359133720398,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the relationship between Joan Maragall and Novalis?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8171261548995972,
            "question": "What was the name of the person who influenced Joan Maragall?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.677216112613678,
            "question": "Who was a source of inspiration for Joan Maragall?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.639535129070282,
            "question": "Who had a significant impact on Joan Maragall's writing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6123936772346497,
            "question": "Name the literary figure that inspired Joan Maragall."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5798191428184509,
            "question": "Joan Maragall's work was affected by whom?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5081580877304077,
            "question": "What is Novalis known for?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Joan Maragall was influenced by Novalis.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4914_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Joan Maragall's work was affected by whom?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4914_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name the literary figure that inspired Joan Maragall.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4914_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who had a significant impact on Joan Maragall's writing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4914_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4914_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4914_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4914_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4914_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4914_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4914_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4914_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4914_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4914_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4914_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple, as it is stated that Joan Maragall was influenced early on by the poetry of German Romantic poets Goethe and Novalis."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Joan Maragall was influenced by Novalis.\" Specifically, it mentions that \"Joan Maragall studied law and literature at the University of Barcelona and was influenced early on by the poetry of German Romantic poets Goethe and Novalis, whose works he also translated.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}